Made in ABC
Is it time already?
Yes, I'm sorry.
It looks like it's over.
Thank you very much.
Let me have a drink.
Mr. Yoshida.
Mama. Mama.
Wake up.
Oh, Mr. Yoshida.
Welcome.
The president of the company I'm working at.
The president of the company I'm working at right now.
I'm the president.
I'm a big fan of the president.
I'm glad you're here.
Yuga said it's this way.
That's why I came to see you.
Isn't that right, president?
Well, here you go.
Lena.
Here you go.
Well, this young lady.
Yes.
I am.
Mr. Sasaoka.
Yes.
Is the company in Wangan and your home in this neighborhood?
Yes, yes, yes.
Even if it's a neighborhood, it's a small town.
What's wrong?
No, no.
Oh, president.
Yes.
You can't touch my Lena.
I'm sorry.
I think it's my daughter.
Oh, president.
Do you have a daughter?
There are two now.
The top is 24 years old.
The bottom is a fourth grader.
What about your child?
What are you doing?
No.
Oh, there's Mama's song.
Oh.
Oh, I'm going to sing.
I'll bring this.
Yeah.
Number 18.
It's number 18.
Teacher.
Lena isn't a high school student, is she?
No.
Julia, thank you.
It's bad, isn't it?
It's okay.
It's not like I did anything.
It doesn't matter.
It's okay.
Can you do it?
Good morning.
Be careful.
Don't spread your bike.
Okay.
Be careful.
Good morning.
Don't bump into each other.
It's not over yet.
Don't ride it yet.
Hey, hey.
Don't ride it.
It's just barely.
It's barely.
Hey, it's dangerous.
Thank you.
The house is good, so don't worry about it.
Have a nice day.
Oh, man.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry.
I'll call you right away.
You said you couldn't do it.
Fix your bike quickly.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry.
Good morning.
What about the bike?
You're the only one working with the teacher at this house.
It has nothing to do with club activities or training.
Anyway, I wonder why Rio is a member of the basketball club.
She doesn't seem to be interested in sports.
I'm sorry.
I'm not interested in sports at all.
If you weren't a teacher, you could have gone on a trip with everyone.
You should have gone with Dad.
I can only go with him now.
You can't.
If you get married and have children, you'll be more important.
Marriage?
What?
I wonder if I can get married.
Hey, what about Seiya?
Well, well, well, well.
Don't waste time on the training.
You'll be dumped.
He is in America right now.
Make sure you make a phone call.
I can't contact him so easily because he is overseas.
You're a good teacher.
Can't you do something about club activities?
Mom is noisy.
But...
I have a reason.
Not only practice, but also schedule adjustment.
I'm not sure if I'm responsible for everything.
I don't know if I'm responsible for everything.
Well, it's up to the director.
It's a fundamental problem.
Do you have to do club activities?
What?
If you do it, you should do it with the club team.
You should pay for it.
I see.
It's all about the management of the teachers.
If you think about it, it's a terrible burden to be run by the director.
Club activities...
I wonder if it's really necessary for students.
Certainly.
Isn't it okay if it's not?
Well, in the world,
there are a lot of people who want to be a club director and a teacher.
Especially the baseball club that aims to support the school and the national tournament.
Soccer club.
After all, club activities are important other than studying.
Hey, teacher.
What was the club activity like in your high school days?
It's not like this if it's a regular high school in the country.
That's right.
When I was in high school, I really wanted to go to the national tournament.
Was it hard this time?
No, it was pretty hard.
I was surprised when I noticed it.
But I was serious about my life.
I didn't hate it at all.
It's a different time than now.
No, no, no.
It's four or five years ago, right?
Certainly.
But I feel like something has definitely changed before this corona.
Something has changed and that's how it works now.
That's right.
You know something, right?
Ministry of Education and Science.
But I don't think it's just the teachers.
What?
It's hard to work.
Everything in the world is black.
Payment is hard everywhere.
It's just a part of a big company.
What's going on with the white promotion?
No, no, no.
I'm doing my best.
Really?
Hey, don't say that the teachers are decent.
No, I think it's a good thing to have a good job.
No, no, no.
They say that the workers who are screaming for a job reform are the most jobless.
Even so, the public is invincible as long as it doesn't collapse.
It's private, so it's not public.
Oh, I see.
Oh, and you know what?
You just have to pay for it.
That's right.
But you know what?
I like to teach, so I choose teachers.
When the students understand and say it's fun, I'm so happy.
Oh, that's great.
Well, I'm sure the direction of the day off is impossible.
But even if the pay is cheap, I like it and choose it.
I'm convinced of that.
That's why the era of doing things is over.
Wait, wait, wait.
It's time to start.
Dad's?
Dad, hurry up.
The best company of the night is...
Sasaoka Hideki, who plays the role of the representative, is working.
It's Kabuchigayaki.
I'm sorry.
He is so embarrassed.
It's so funny.
Do you want to go out for dinner?
I'll go, but...
But what?
I don't want to walk in front of everyone.
Why not?
I'm sick of it.
Are you okay?
This means that you were very rich.
I don't like it.
What?
Homura, can I talk about my opinion?
What's your opinion?
The company of Sasaoka Sensei's father may lead society to change.
I don't believe it.
What's wrong?
I haven't seen this.
It's really bad, Rio's father.
Did your father do something bad?
No, he was the president of a famous company.
Really?
Look at him.
Who is he?
He's amazing.
He's the president.
He must be rich.
To be continued...
You were a very young lady.
That's not true.
My father's company was established when I was in middle school.
Until then, I was just an ordinary girl.
But that's not a bad thing, is it?
What is?
A bodyguard.
Good morning.
That's right.
We had a three-way meeting the other day.
By the way, I saw it on TV the other day.
You're young, but you're mature.
That's easy to understand.
I thought I was different from the average person from the beginning.
Great!
There was so much of a bodyguard society from the beginning.
The person who was a bodyguard changed easily.
A bodyguard is the other way around.
It's a sign of strong attachment to children.
I see.
In other words, everyone has one thing in common.
Is it possible to get a job at your father's company?
That's it.
But to be honest, it's hard.
I can't do anything about it myself.
Hey!
You're doing the same as usual.
I'm sorry.
I can't stop it.
As I said the other day.
I promised you I'd lower the volume a little.
I'm going to get excited like this.
I'm going to get excited.
I'm going to have a lot of fun in the city.
I know.
It's about every year.
It's not a joke.
I'm sorry.
Mr. Hoshihara.
I thought it would be nice when you came.
I heard that you liked it.
It's a famous financial company.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to do that.
Monpei and Kureima may change for one reason or another.
But it was good.
It went well in the three-way meeting.
Yes.
So far.
Even if it's a little smooth,
I'm sure it will hurt if you are careless.
I think so.
I think the young people will solve it soon.
Do you understand?
When I was young.
I have to take care of the car.
Then it's just right.
Listen to me.
It will be helpful to the health care team.
Sit down.
Please.
I was in a class when I was young.
Most of the health care staff are dissatisfied with young teachers.
It was written in the questionnaire.
I was shocked.
I have no choice but to do this.
I called the parents who said they were dissatisfied.
What are you dissatisfied with?
What is wrong with the current situation?
Are you serious?
Then I was surprised.
Everyone said the same thing.
I was worried and dissatisfied.
Why did you write that?
At that time, I was a senior in the second year.
The class was up and the health care staff were friendly.
One of them started to make noise.
Everyone was excited.
Let's share our feelings.
I see.
That's why everyone was dissatisfied.
That's terrible.
What I learned from here is not to deal with a big wave.
It's important to face each other.
It's important to face each other with each child.
I think this is important.
As expected of Mr. Kimoto.
It's a hot health care system.
Thank you very much.
It's good to be a parent.
If you live a long life like me,
there are many people in the neighborhood.
When I was young, there were a lot of people.
It's been more than 30 years.
It's time.
Let's get ready for class.
I have 13 minutes.
Me too.
Sit down and listen.
Sit down.
Okay.
Good.
It's a claim.
Most of them are for the sake of the child.
Or the first wrong response.
Or the wrong button.
That's most of them.
Most of them.
There are.
The real ones.
The real ones?
This one.
They try to solve it with money.
That's the main thing.
There are such people.
By the way.
I heard that my classmate Okido's father is like that.
It's true.
It's a student who feels like he's sitting on a string.
Okido's place.
Do you know anything about Mr. Kyoto?
Yes.
I heard the rumor.
It's from Mr. Toyoshima.
He didn't respond to the first meeting.
He refused the Zoom meeting.
I told him I was going to see him.
What is it?
Please say something.
It's okay.
Is it okay?
I'll tell you this.
You can't give him a random signal.
He's not doing anything wrong.
He's being honest.
And you can't go out alone.
Please tell him this.
Mr. Kyoto won't go out with you, will he?
I don't think he'll go out with the police right away.
I don't think he'll do anything.
It's okay.
I'm sorry.
I just got a call.
It's Nagatega.
Hello?
It's been a while.
It's from Keiki Iwata.
Did he just get a call?
His Japanese was getting worse.
Right?
But he really went to Okida.
What should I do?
I'm scared.
I don't want to go.
Why did I tell him not to go?
Good morning.
It's Satsu.
What is this?
It's cute.
It's Satsu.
I want a girlfriend too.
Let's do a matching app.
Is that okay?
It's not good, but there's no girl I like in this school.
There's no girl I like.
Homura, the app is in English.
Don't come.
I want a girl I like.
What are you doing?
Miyasaka.
Is there a girl you like?
What?
Seriously?
I don't know.
What?
Miyasaka, can I talk to you?
You don't want to talk to me?
You're a band man.
Yamamoto, you play guitar.
Shut up.
The history of the band is proven.
Do you know the song?
I don't want to hear it.
Tell me.
The song is...
How do you know that?
Rio-sensei.
Hello, sensei.
Hello, Miyasaka.
I remembered.
I wanted to ask you something.
What do you think about the band?
What's wrong?
I want to know what a band man is like.
That's good.
Really?
I have to study.
I'm going to the staff room.
In high school, there was a teacher who played the band.
There was.
Did you like him?
I didn't like him that much.
But...
I thought he was cool.
I admired everyone.
That's right.
I can't get out.
Are you going to Okido and Sawaiya?
Yes.
They're both absent, but I haven't heard from them.
I don't have class until 3 o'clock.
Shall I go to Okido's house?
Are you going now?
Is it okay?
I'm fine.
If I can talk to his father,
I'll tell him about the three-way interview.
Really?
I'll go to Sawaiya's house.
I'll call you if anything happens.
Thank you.
Okay.
It's okay to hit me.
That's right.
I'm going.
Sawaiya.
I was going to ask you about your family.
What?
I want to talk to your mother.
No.
Can you not come to see her?
But...
You don't need to talk to her.
But it's important.
It's about Shino in the future.
So...
Teacher.
You don't have to work so hard for me.
You just have to live more comfortably.
Hey, wait.
That's right.
Do you get along with your father?
Yeah.
We get along, but why?
No, nothing.
Hey, Sawaiya.
It's Yamazoi.
Mr Okido!
Okido.
Hey.
What are you doing at school?
Who are them?
Where are they from?
From when I was in middle school.
Let's go to school.
Now?
Yeah.
I'm going to skip school today.
If you're late, you'll regret it.
I'll quit.
You've worked so hard.
I'm not saying I want to go.
You're not a kid anymore.
You have to get a good job.
I'm looking for a job.
Where's your parents?
Do you talk to them?
Not really.
That's fine.
It's my life.
Yeah.
I don't have a life where I can talk like that.
Who?
My father.
Ok.
Let's go to school.
No.
If I miss you, I'll get mad at you.
What?
You don't want to get mad at me, so you want me to go to school?
Leave me alone.
You're not a kid anymore.
I'm not a kid anymore.
You smoke.
I don't.
You smoke a lot.
To be honest, you smoke, right?
I don't.
Let's go to school.
Stop it.
You're disgusting.
Don't say that to the teacher.
I'll kill you.
Hey.
Can a teacher say that to a student?
You're so cute.
You're bad, but you say that.
Stop it.
You're so cute.
I get it.
Let's go.
He smokes.
I was going to do it, so I won't be surprised.
You're right.
What should we do?
We can't just leave him alone.
You can leave him alone.
But...
He's gone.
Excuse me.
What is it?
It's nothing.
Damn it.
It stinks.
It doesn't.
Give me a cigarette.
Is that a cigarette?
No, I don't smoke.
You're not allowed to go home.
School?
I'm not a criminal.
If you smoke.
So tell me if you find evidence.
That's an excuse for the criminal.
That's an excuse.
I'll talk to my dad.
He's gone.
He's not coming.
I'm going.
If he can't come, I'll go.
I'm so cool.
Me?
When will you be cool?
I can't be cool.
Is Seira not here?
Seira?
She quit.
She quit?
Why?
Did she go to another store?
I don't know the details.
But I'm here.
Why isn't she coming?
I'm home.
Lena, why didn't you come?
I wanted to help you.
Mai, I'm home.
You're so cute.
Yu, I'm home.
I'm home.
Stop it.
Good night.
I'm tired.
I'm leaving. Call me if you need me.
Going to your boyfriend's?
I got a gift for breakfast.
Sato said he went to Aomori.
I know.
Good night.
You didn't drink today?
I quit.
It's about the three-way interview.
You quit?
Did you quit Ginza?
I was told you'd come to see me.
I'm not a kid.
I'm a housewife.
Did you quit Ginza?
Did something happen?
Did you work at another store?
It was a matter of time.
What do you mean?
High school students.
You don't know unless you say it.
You're a jerk.
I do what I want to do.
I don't know what to do.
What?
I have to do it right.
Then what do you do?
What?
Do you work at another store?
I can't sell it.
You have an exam next year.
What are you going to do?
If you think that way,
don't be a jerk.
I'm not a jerk.
You're a jerk.
It's embarrassing.
Don't make a loud voice.
It's scary to see kids get up.
Why did you lie to me?
Why are you laughing?
Are you serious?
You're a kid who doesn't know
the essence of human beings.
You can't laugh.
You're an adult.
Don't touch me.
You're a kid, so you can laugh.
You're cute.
I'm going.
Call me if you need anything.
Bye.
Shit!
Good job.
Let's go have some fun.
Bye-bye!
Let's go.
This is good.
Yes.
Are you going to meet with the security guard?
I'll go after I clean up.
Call me if you need anything.
Thank you.
This is...
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Okay, let's go.
I have no choice but to come to Parao.
Hello.
It's Shikato.
The bicycle is gone.
That's right.
It's over there.
Okay.
Did you come running?
I didn't think you'd come.
My dad's not here.
Is he at work?
Well...
You said he knew we'd come today.
I didn't think you'd come.
Why?
What's your dad's job?
What does he do specifically?
I don't know.
What time does he finish?
You have to talk to your dad.
I don't...
No.
You can't.
You have to talk to him.
Hey, Kouken!
Okido!
Let's go.
What?
To my dad's place.
To your dad's place?
Hi.
Hi, Kouken.
Long time no see.
I'm going to talk to you again.
Nice to meet you.
What?
Wait.
Kouken, we don't need food.
Welcome.
We don't need ramen.
What?
What's that?
Teachers at school.
They want to talk to their dad.
What?
Dad.
Excuse me.
Well...
I'm Sasaoka, Kouken's partner.
I'm Yamazue, Fukutani's partner.
Excuse me.
I wanted to talk to you.
What do you mean you want to talk to me?
You're a teacher at school.
I told you not to talk to me.
You're too strong.
What?
Excuse me.
I didn't know you were doing this kind of work.
I didn't know...
What did you think your dad was doing?
Well...
You're a good girl.
You're good at contacting people.
You're busy, aren't you?
Hey.
Kouken's teacher is here.
I'm going to close the store.
Now?
I understand.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry.
I can't.
When the customers come back,
I'll close the store.
Well...
It's been quite a while since I closed the store.
The store is at 11 o'clock.
After that, I'll clean up.
It's 3 or 4 o'clock tomorrow night.
Can you wait a moment?
Yes.
Can I go now?
Hey.
Please go home.
Yes.
Excuse me.
Do you drink?
Yes.
It's so scary.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
It's okay.
I just called that idiot.
I'm sorry.
Did you two have dinner?
No.
I didn't notice.
Not yet.
Then can I have ramen?
Yes.
Wait.
Did that idiot do something?
Well...
My father said he couldn't participate in the three-way meeting.
I'm glad it was Zoom.
What's Zoom?
Basically, I don't go to school.
What?
That's...
Since he was in middle school.
Is there a reason?
Did you hear about it?
What?
My story.
No.
Well...
Did you hear about Yakuza?
No.
That's right.
I paid for it five years ago.
Yakuza used to be like this.
When you go to school,
Yakuza's son will make you feel small.
I went to the entrance ceremony in middle school.
As a parent, I was so happy.
But then,
I heard a lot of rumors at school.
I started to get confused.
I started to get along with my seniors.
I did the same thing as I used to do.
I thought it would be bad if I went on like this.
Yakuza's course was so bad.
I didn't want him to be Yakuza.
Yakuza is the worst.
He's good at deceiving people.
He's dirty for money.
But I'm not Yakuza.
I can't show it.
That's why I started it.
I wanted him to be Yakuza.
I knew it.
It's hard to get out of this country.
Yakuza is strict,
but he can't have a bank account for a while.
He's doing it for his friends.
He's working hard for his son.
But his son is a loser.
It's not going well.
Is he doing something bad?
Is he going to school?
He's taking a break from school.
I told him not to hang out with his bad friends.
He was bothering me.
I'm sorry.
No, no, no.
Yes?
Yes.
What does your father want you to do after graduation?
He says he's going to get a job.
As a person who has been through a lot,
I really want him to go to college.
Is that so?
You can't go to college in Gogen, can you?
Well, that's right.
Tell me the truth.
I think it's going to be a lot of work.
Is that so?
But if he is serious,
there's a chance.
What?
Are you serious?
Is there a chance that he can go to college in Gogen?
It's up to me.
It's up to my own motivation.
Is there a chance that you can go to college in Gogen?
I think it's ridiculous to be in an educated society.
But as a person who has been through an uneducated life like me,
I admire him.
I want him to have a great life.
Is that so?
He might be able to go to college.
Hey,
he's the child I gave birth to.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Here you go.
Thank you for waiting.
Thank you very much.
Please eat.
I hope you like it.
Thank you for the food.
I see.
I have to do my best.
It's good.
It's really good.
Yes.
It was delicious.
I really like that kind of taste.
Me too.
But I was a little surprised.
It's the time when his father suddenly cried.
Yes.
But it's like that, isn't it?
I understand what you want to say.
We're on our back, aren't we?
We're on our back.
We have to do our best.
That's right.
I don't want to talk to you.
Mayu,
you're like a mother these days.
Do you live with your mother?
That's what you say, isn't it?
If you think so,
don't say that kind of thing.
It doesn't make sense to say that.
Don't say that and look at yourself.
I want to look at you.
Shut up.
No way.
Are you serious?
Thank you.
You came.
I'm glad.
Why did you know my contact information?
My mother taught me.
When I went to the store the other day.
That old hag.
Why?
It's a good thing, isn't it?
Because it's a good job.
I'll give this to you first.
10,000 yen.
What are you going to do?
I'll pay you 20,000 yen later.
Please subscribe to the channel.
If you want to enjoy the previous episodes,
please watch it on UNEXT and Netflix.
It's really bad.
Let's watch it from the beginning.
How is it?
This, this, this.
I think this will expand into an adventure.
Travel?